Most people associate virtual reality with the world of gaming or entertainment.
大多数人把虚拟现实与游戏或娱乐领域联系在一起。
What is all the fuss, you may wonder, about a futuristic contraption you wear on your head that makes you look like a creature from Star Wars?
你可能会想，对于一个戴在头上、让你看起来像《星球大战》里的生物的未来派装置，到底有什么大惊小怪的呢？
But this emerging technology has been spreading rapidly into many other areas and could fundamentally change your life in the future.
但是这项新兴技术已经迅速传播到许多其他领域，并且在未来可能会从根本上改变你的生活。
Virtual reality, or VR, is a computer-generated technology that creates a three-dimensional digital world that you can not only see and observe, but explore and interact with it as if you are there.
虚拟现实，简称VR，是一种由计算机生成的技术，它创造了一个三维数字世界，你不仅可以看到和观察这个世界，还可以探索并与之互动，就好像你身临其境一样。
Once you put on the special equipment - a helmet or goggles with a screen inside or gloves fitted with sensors - you become immersed in the virtual world.
一旦你戴上特殊设备-一个里面有屏幕的头盔或护目镜，或者装有传感器的手套-你就会沉浸在虚拟世界中。
VR now has serious applications in fields as wide-ranging as business and medicine.
VR现在在商业和医学等广泛的领域都有重要应用。
VR has already proved effective as a training tool as it simulates real experiences.
VR作为一种培训工具已经被证明是有效的，因为它可以模拟真实的体验。
One simulation programme educates young drivers about the dangers of bad driving.
一个模拟程序可以教育年轻司机不良驾驶的危险性。
Participants experience a dangerous car journey and a virtual accident.
参与者会体验一次危险的驾车旅程和一场虚拟事故。
It is now being used to train surgeons.
现在它也被用于培训外科医生。
Connor Pierce of Samsung's IT for UK and Ireland thinks it will impinge on all walks of life: "We'll socialise via VR, we will do business via VR, we'll have VR team-meetings, we'll have VR education, museums will have virtual reality experiences...".
三星英国和爱尔兰信息技术部门的康纳·皮尔斯认为它将影响各行各业：“我们将通过VR进行社交，通过VR开展业务，我们会有VR团队会议，我们会有VR教育，博物馆也会有虚拟现实体验……
Its benefits have been felt in the field of psychology and the treatment of mental health patients.
”。它的益处也体现在了心理学领域以及心理健康患者的治疗方面。
Professor Daniel Freeman at the Warnford Hospital in Oxford uses it to treat vertigo and other anxiety disorders.
牛津大学沃恩福德医院的丹尼尔·弗里曼教授用它来治疗眩晕和其他焦虑症。
He explains that by exposing patients to what they fear most in a virtual environment and showing them that nothing bad happens, they can eventually overcome their panic.
他解释说，通过让患者在虚拟环境中面对他们最害怕的东西，并向他们表明不会发生什么坏事，他们最终可以克服恐惧。
In the world of work too, VR may change our lives dramatically.
在工作领域，VR也可能会极大地改变我们的生活。
Working individually at home, we can connect to our colleagues in a virtual space.
在家独自工作时，我们可以在虚拟空间中与同事联系。
We can be at home and at the office at the same time.
我们可以同时在家和在办公室。
For the first time, we can really be in two places at once.
我们第一次真正能够同时身处两个地方。
Some VR developers predict that the impact of VR could be as significant as the internet or mobile phones.
一些VR开发者预测，VR的影响可能会和互联网或手机一样重大。
Google alone has sold 2 million cardboard VR headsets in the last two years.
仅谷歌一家公司在过去两年里就售出了200万个纸板VR头戴设备。
Is a new age of reality about to dawn?
一个新的现实时代即将开始吗？